Danny Pink... is dead.
We're here to get your boyfriend
back from the dead.
Those are tombs. Water tombs.
Why would anyone go to
so much trouble?
You're dead and...
and this is what's next.
A Gallifreyan hard drive.
Time Lord technology.
Do you know the key strategic
weakness of the human race?
The dead outnumber
the living.
Who are you?
Oh, you know who I am.
I'm Missy.
I couldn't very well
keep calling myself
The Master, now - could I?
Stop! You can't kill me!
Incorrect.
I'm a target of strategic value.
Alive, I'm a tactical advantage.
Dead, I'm your biggest mistake.
You don't know who I am!
You are Clara Oswald. You are human.
You are unimportant.
Incorrect. You see, THAT is what
you're supposed to think.
THAT is what everybody thinks.
You are Clara Oswald.
Clara Oswald is a cover story -
a disguise. There is NO Clara Oswald.
~ Identify. ~ Oh, don't be so slow,
it's embarrassing.
Who could fool you like this?
Who could hide right under your nose?
Who could change their face
any time they want?
Hmm! You see, I'm not Clara Oswald.
Clara Oswald has never existed.
Identify.
I'm the Doctor.
Look at them! My boys!
Cybermen, in broad daylight?
You think people won't notice?
Photos with the big metal men -
one pound!
Oh, honey!
There you go.
Oh, cool. Cool!
New York. Paris. Rome. Marrakech.
Brisbane. Glasgow. Everywhere.
Anywhere. Me and my boys.
We're going viral.
Would you like me to take a picture?
Sorry, selfies are never as good,
are they?
And you're having a lovely moment.
Hang on!
~ No, just... ~ Nice bow tie.
Bow ties are cool. Big smiles, and...
now!
Move, move, move! Stand by.
Surround target.
Hold back!
Afternoon. You've picked
a lovely day for it.
My, don't you look shiny!
~ Haircut? ~ Bit of a trim.
Might want to do your roots.
~ The woman. ~ Yes, ma'am. ~ Kate Stewart.
Divorcee, mother of two, keen
gardener, outstanding bridge player.
Also chief scientific officer,
Unified Intelligence Taskforce -
who currently have you surrounded.
Human weaponry is not
effective against Cyber technology.
Sorry, you left this behind on one
of your previous attempts.
So now that I have your attention,
welcome to the only planet in the
universe where we get to say this.
He's on the payroll.
Am I?
Well, technically.
~ How much? ~ Sh! Any questions?
Back, back, everyone, back!
Oh, my God!
Is it supposed to do that?
Is that new?
A sun roof on St Paul's?!
Yes, I'd say that was new!
There's going to be mass panic.
Everyone in London can see that.
Everyone in London just clapped and
went "whee"!
Hush, I'm trying to count.
~ 87, I think. ~ OCD.
91.
Queen of evil.
How could St Paul's be full of 91
Cybermen and nobody noticed?
Dimensional engineering - one space
folded inside another.
Bigger on the inside.
Easy if you're a Time Lord.
Mostly deploying south,
a smaller number east.
~ Yep, but one straight up.
~ So 91 isn't a coincidence?
Of course it isn't.
Osgood? 91 - explain.
91 areas of significant population
density in the British Isles.
That's one Cyberman for every city
and major town.
It's happening everywhere, all over
the world, right now!
Sweet planet, this.
I think I might keep it.
One Cyberman per city. What could
they hope to accomplish?
Doctor!
~ Has it exploded? ~ More than that.
Cybermen don't just blow themselves
up for no good reason, dear -
they're not human.
~ If it isn't exploding,
what's it doing? ~ Pollinating.
Falling like rain
into the cracks of the Earth.
~ Well, this IS a bit exciting!
~ What's happening?
Well, to cut a long story short,
it looks like we might all be going
home.
Home? From the afterlife?
Well, when I said "afterlife",
I was being a tiny bit poetic.
And Nethersphere is just a cool name
we come up with during a spit-ball.
What is this place?
Well, you have to
think of it as a data cloud.
You know, for storing data.
In this case, it's the storage
of recently deceased minds.
We're in a cloud?
A sort of cloud, yeah.
And what's happening to it?
What happens to any cloud
when it starts to rain.
Are you telling me we're going back?
What, back to our bodies?
And the extra good news is...
there's been a bit of an upgrade.
The dead are coming home, Doctor.
All shiny and new.
In 24 hours the human race
as you know it will cease to exist.
What are you doing? Explain.
Tell me now!
Oh! That was nice, must do it again.
No. No, no, no, no, I need
to talk to her! I need her awake.
Agh!
No. No, no, stupid!
Stupid! No, no! Agh!
The first protocol is implemented.
We're good to go.
You just have to let it take you.
Ow!
What did he say?
He said, "Guard the graveyards."
That's weird. Look at that!
How come it's only raining
INSIDE the graveyard?
'We are being told that
'these metal men
are known as Cybermen, but
'unlike the accounts we have on file,
they now have the ability to fly.
'Similar reports are coming
in from all over the world.
'Flying Cybermen
are here on a global scale.
'Ministers are telling us...'
'.. to remain calm.
'These Cybermen
don't seem to be attacking us,
'at least not in any
conventional fashion.
'Eyewitnesses have reported
seeing them flying in the sky...'
Hello?
Agh!
Right. Be careful with it.
Be careful.
Take your time.
Kate?
What's with the handcuffs?
I'm sorry. In the event of an alien
incursion on this scale,
protocols are in place.
Your co-operation is to be ensured
and your unreliability assumed.
You have a history.
You don't have a future without me!
Do you think your father
would've done this?
We both know he absolutely would.
Who is she?
Long story. Where's Clara?
Clara Oswald, your assistant?
My friend.
She was with me in St Paul's.
The team's still on site
but they've been unable to gain
access to the building.
I want her found and brought here.
I need her with me.
Then give the order.
As soon as you're on board Boat One
your word is law.
Quite literally.
You got the TARDIS out, then?
Yes, and St Paul's locked down.
~ Where are we going? Cloudbase?
~ You mean the Valiant?
Cloudbase was Thunderbirds.
Too conspicuous. We need your
location concealed, not advertised.
From now on you're a moving target.
Ah, I see you're bringing Daddy
along, too. That's very sweet.
Sir!
Oh, don't do that. You look like
you're self-concussing,
which would explain all of military
history, now I think about it.
Colonel Ahmed, sir.
Privileged to meet you.
Love your outfit, Colonel Ahmed.
Are you in the Scouts?
Are you a Man Scout?
I didn't know they had those.
~ It was Captain Scarlet. ~ Sorry?
Not Thunderbirds.
Oh, God, so it was!
My confidence is growing
every minute.
The President is on board.
Mind you, me and Sylvia Anderson,
you've never seen a foxtrot like it.
Hang on a second. The President?
We don't want Americans
bobbing around the place.
They'll only start praying.
Not the President of America, sir.
The President of Earth.
~ There isn't one. ~ There is now.
The incursion protocols have been
agreed internationally.
In the event of full-scale invasion,
an Earth president is
inducted immediately,
with complete authority
over every nation state.
There was only
one practical candidate.
That's your answer for everything,
isn't it? Vote for an idiot.
If you say so, Mr President(!)
So long as you're on this plane,
you're the Commander-in-Chief
of every army on Earth.
Every world leader is currently
awaiting your instructions.
You are the Chief Executive Officer
of the human race.
Any questions?
'This is your captain speaking.
Please prepare for take-off.'
Well, gentlemen. Where to start?
I was born on the planet Gallifrey,
in the constellation
of Kasterborous.
I'm a Time Lord, but my Prydonian
privileges were revoked
when I stole a time capsule
and ran away.
Currently piloting a Type 40 TARDIS.
Married four times, all deceased.
My children and grandchildren
are missing, and I assume, dead.
I have a non-Gallifreyan daughter,
created via genetic transfer.
How much more do you need?
I'm the Doctor!
This information is not proof.
We require proof.
~ How about my name? ~ Explain.
Well, my name isn't "Doctor", is it?
I don't even really have a doctorate.
Well, Glasgow University,
but then I accidentally graduated in
the wrong century, so technically...
This information
cannot be confirmed.
You are Clara Oswald.
Ah, no! I'm not!
Your deception is intended to
prolong your life.
Your presence has not been ordered.
Correct.
You are Clara Oswald.
Oh, seriously, this is getting old.
Look, there is no Clara Oswald.
I invented her. I made her up.
Born 23rd November, 1986.
Yeah, I chose that date.
Always liked it.
Father - David James Oswald.
Mother - Elena Alison Oswald.
Stories. Stories. Stories.
I made them up.
Look, ask anybody who knows me.
I am an incredible liar.
Correct.
No order was given.
You are not under Cyber control.
Correct.
Why are you still alive?
You saved me!
I saved Gallifrey.
Yes, Gallifrey too, I suppose.
There's always collateral damage
with you and me.
It's our Paris.
Gallifrey's lost
in another dimension.
Yes and no.
Meaning?
Yes, it's in another dimension.
No, it's not lost.
You know where it is?
Yep!
You know the best part
about knowing?
(Not... telling... you!)
'Mr President, sir,
we're ready for you up here.'
Remember all those years, when all
you wanted to do was rule the world?
~ On my way.
~ 'Thank you, Mr President.'
Piece of cake!
Oh, erm.
It's her little device thingy.
I thought there might be useful
information on it. Who is she?
You'd never believe me
if I told you.
Cos I thought she might be the
Master, regenerated into female form.
Your childhood friend, responsible
for a number of previous incursions.
That was fairly quick.
We do have files on all
our ex-prime ministers.
She wasn't even the worst.
~ Doctor, there's something
nobody's talking about. ~ Which is?
The clouds caused by
the exploding Cybermen -
they haven't dispersed,
they're still there.
In fact, they've expanded and are
covering almost all the land masses.
We're all looking at the graveyards.
Maybe we should be looking up.
What do you think?
~ All of time and space. ~ Sorry?
Just something for your bucket list.
'.. localised rain in
the cemeteries has resulted in
'what can only be described as
"disturbances" to the soil.
'Extraordinary eyewitness
accounts are claiming that
'silver creatures are climbing
from the graves...'
These scenes are being repeated
everywhere, every cemetery,
every mortuary, every funeral home,
every hospital -
the dead are returning to life
as Cybermen.
'.. the public are being advised
to stay away from all cemeteries.'
Hello?
We've done heat scans of some of
the cemeteries and, in each case,
only a handful of Cybermen
have so far emerged.
~ But every individual burial site
is active. ~ Active?
~ Hatching. ~ More are coming.
Potentially millions.
So the rain caused all that
in just a few hours?
It wasn't rain, Man Scout!
It was pollen. Cyber-pollen.
Every tiny particle of a Cyberman
contains the plans
to make another Cyberman.
All it has to do is to make
a contact with compatible,
living organic matter, and bang -
full conversion.
But if they have learned
how to convert the dead...
(That's what she was doing!)
(That's what 3W was for!)
She creates an all-new paranoia
among the super-rich about dying.
She exploits the wealth and the
mortal remains of selected idiots,
so she can create a whole new race
of Cybermen.
Cybermen who can recruit corpses.
Throw away your guns,
Man Scout, it's all over.
How can you win a war against an
enemy that can weaponise the dead?
They're not attacking, apart from
isolated incidents.
~ They're just wandering about.
~ They're newborns. Give them time.
Why were you there this morning,
why were you already attacking?
Been investigating 3W for a while
then we got a tip-off.
From a woman with a Scottish accent.
Can't play to the gallery unless
there's a gallery and here I am.
Dead bodies don't have minds,
of course,
but she's been upgrading dying minds
to a hard drive for a long time.
So she upgrades the hardware,
then she updates the software.
What do you mean "a long time"?
How long?
Well, she must have
a TARDIS somewhere,
~ so as long as she likes, the past,
the future... ~ How long, Doctor?
How long has the human race
had a concept of an afterlife?
Turns out, the afterlife is real.
And it's emptying.
Every graveyard on planet Earth
is about to burst its banks.
♪ Hey, Missy, you're so fine,
you're so fine you blow my mind
♪ Hey, Missy
♪ Hey.. ♪ Excuse me.
Hi. Can I tell you something
really important?
What?
(I have to whisper it.)
(It's, like, so important
to everyone on this plane.)
~ You'll get in trouble if you don't
listen. ~ Right, If it was important,
~ why would you tell us?
~ Well, look at me, I'm bananas.
(Come on.) Just a wee bit closer.
Just a little closer. The Doctor
will be really impressed
if you learn my secrets.
You can come a bit closer than that.
Come on, stop mucking about.
Don't be shy.
You don't smell half as bad
as you think you do.
~ There are two armed men directly
behind you. ~ (Yeah, yeah, yeah.)
If you've got something to say,
just say it.
(I'm going to kill you in a minute.)
I'm not even kidding.
You're going to be as dead as a fish
on a slab any second now,
all floppy and making smells.
(But don't tell the boys.)
(This is our secret girl plan.)
~ Why would you bother killing me?
I'm not even important. ~ Oh, silly!
Why does one pop a balloon?
Because you're pretty.
You should have a bit more
confidence in yourself.
~ OK. Sorry, I've got work to do.
~ All right, fine.
You get on.
You get that finished. Would a
countdown help you focus at all?
~ No, that's OK. ~ Ten. Don't be scared
yet, cos I'm still in double figures.
~ I'm not scared. ~ Nine. Well, no,
of course you're not,
cos you know you're dying,
anyway. Eight.
Human beings are born dying.
Your life spans are hilarious.
Please be quiet.
Seven. You know from the minute
you slop out,
you're rotting, decaying.
The stench of you - phew!
I'm never going to get this
place clean.
~ Three. ~ Three?!
I'm accelerating for
dramatic effect. Oh!
What's THAT in your pocket?
There's nothing in my...
Oh, my giddy aunt.
~ The quiet ones are the worst.
~ Well, those aren't mine.
Hmm...
Then they must be mine.
Say something nice.
Missy, the Master,
whatever you call yourself,
I promise, I'm much more useful
to you alive.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
That's definitely true, that is
a good point well made.
I'm proud of you, sister.
But did I mention...
bananas!
Pop.
Ah...
.. thanks for being yummy.
Whoo-oo!
Mr President, you need
to get back in your seat.
I don't like being the president,
people keep saluting.
I'm never going to salute back.
Do you know, that was always my
dad's big ambition -
to get you to salute him,
just once.
He should've asked.
~ Doctor, what are you looking at?
~ The clouds.
Still there.
So what else have they got?
Oh, dear Lord!
There's a Cyberman out there
on the fuselage.
But, on the plus side,
it's not turbulence.
She's out!
Who let her out?!
What's it doing? Where did it go?
What can one Cyberman do to a plane?
Oh, she was really scared,
it's classic.
Have you got any more friends
I can play with?
Locate hive...
Locate...
.. hive...
Locate hive...
Are you the one that brought me here?
Affirmative.
~ So you know who I am, right?
~ You are not the Doctor.
Of course I'm not the Doctor.
I was lying to stay alive.
But how do I know so much about him?
~ You are his associate. ~ No, I'm not.
I'm not his associate.
I'm his best friend.
Right now, his best friend,
anywhere in the universe.
Have you got any sort of
Cyber-Internet in there because,
really, you should look it up.
~ Look up what happens to you, if you
harm me. ~ Where is the Doctor?
What, you think I would give up
the Doctor? Don't be daft.
I would never, ever,
give up the Doctor.
Because he is my best friend, too.
He is the closest person to me
in this whole world.
He is the man I will always forgive,
always trust,
the one man I would never, ever
lie to.
Danny?
Danny Pink is dead.
Help me.
Oh, my God.
Danny...
Help me.
I am so sorry.
I need you to do something for me.
I can't do it myself.
What is that?
It's an inhibitor.
It's not activated.
I need you to switch it on.
What does it inhibit?
Emotion.
It deletes emotions.
Please.
I don't want to feel like this.
~ There's more than one. ~ What?
They're all over the plane,
they're pulling it apart!
Oh, o-o-oh.
Ask me.
Shut up!
Ask me! Come on, you know you want
to. You want to know what my plan is.
You'll be surprised.
I've got a gift for you.
You know, I've been up and down
your timeline,
meeting all those silly people
who die to keep you alive.
And you know what I worked out?
~ What you really need! ~ For what?
To know that you're just like me!
Oh, and now it begins.
Doctor, I do believe you're on-call.
Miss Oswald expects.
Who else but the girl
who's got your number? Whoops!
It was you!
~ Ah, hello.
~ Where did you get this number?
'The woman in the shop wrote it
down.'
It's a helpline, isn't it?
Computer helpline, love.
That's the one.
Best helpline in the universe.
You put us together.
I kept you together.
~ Who put that advert in the paper?
~ Who gave you my number?
The woman - the woman in the shop.
Then there's a woman out there who's
very keen that we stay together.
~ Why? ~ Cos she's perfect, innit?
The control freak and the man
who should never be controlled.
You'd go to hell, if she asked.
And she would.
The phone's ringing, Doctor,
can you hear that?
Now that's the sound of your chain
being yanked. Heel, Doctor!
Help me, Doctor!
Help me! Help me, Doctor!
Clara?
Doctor.
With Danny.
~ Danny's dead, Clara. ~ 'Not yet.'
Not quite. But he wants to be.
'Clara...'
Clara?
He's a Cyberman.
'Doctor, Danny's a Cyberman.'
And he's crying.
Doctor, he feels it, he's crying.
Message to Geneva.
Tell them Boat One is going down.
We don't anticipate survivors.
Clara, don't do it,
just don't do it!
It's in his chest.
He says it's an inhibitor.
It can delete emotion, or something.
I know what it does.
If you turn it on,
he'll become a Cyberman.
He's already a Cyberman.
Not yet, he isn't.
He's hurting because I hurt him
and he wants it to stop.
Stop the pain and he'll kill you!
Look, are you going to help me?
Because I can't do this alone.
I'm not going to help you
commit suicide.
Look, the TARDIS can
home in on this call, right?
Either you help me,
or you leave me alone.
Clara? Clara, no...
There's a lot of switches
round the edge.
I'm going to try pressing them all.
OK.
I am so sorry.
Yeah.
Doctor! The Cybermen are in!
The plane's going down!
Oh, great. It's the daughter one.
Do you like her? I like her.
Aaaaaargh!
Why did you do that?
You didn't have to do that!
Oh, don't be so selfish.
I'm going to miss her, too.
In fact, you know what?
Just for that, I'm leaving.
Boys, blow up this plane and,
I don't know... Belgium, yeah?
Kill some Belgians.
Might as well.
They're not even French.
Byeeee!
Aargh!
Aaargh! Argh! Argh!
Aargh... argh...
Well, that's very boring.
Oh, he's just going to...
squish.
What kind of a way is that to die?
That man has NO finesse, none.
Well, it's quite dramatic.
You're an AI interface, kindly
delete your opinions, thank you.
W-W-What's he doing? Is he...?
Is he?
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no. N-Now, that's...
Oh!
Permission to... squeeeee...
Two more to go.
Does it feel any different?
No.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Clara, don't!
Help me.
If you do what you're trying to do,
if you succeed, he will snap you.
~ No. ~ Then he will step over
your broken body and break
another and another and another.
He will never stop.
I will not harm her.
PE...
Sir.
I had a friend once.
We ran together, when I was little.
And I thought we were the same.
But when we grew up, we weren't.
Now, she's trying to
tear the world apart,
and I can't run fast enough to
hold it together. The difference...
.. is this.
Pain is a gift.
Without the capacity for pain,
we can't feel the hurt we inflict.
Are you telling me,
seriously, for real, that you can?
Of course I can.
Then shame on you, Doctor.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Danny, Danny,
I need you to tell me,
what are the clouds going to do?
What is the plan?
~ How would I know?
~ You're part of a hive mind now.
Presumably, that's how you
found Clara.
Just look.
I can't see much.
Look harder.
Clara, watch this.
This is who the Doctor is.
Watch the blood-soaked
old general in action.
I can't see properly, sir,
because this needs activating.
If you want to know what's coming,
you have to switch... it... on.
And didn't all of those beautiful
speeches just disappear
in the face of a tactical advantage?
Sir?
I need to know.
(Yes.)
Yes, you do.
Give me the screwdriver.
~ No. ~ Just do it, Doctor.
Do as you are told.
Typical officer.
Got to keep those hands clean.
Just point and think, yeah?
Yes.
OK.
I wasn't very good at it...
but I did love you.
I loved you, too.
I'm never going to say that again.
Me neither.
Ready?
Yeah.
It feels like I'm killing you.
I'm already dead.
You're here this time at least.
Goodbye, Danny.
Goodbye, Clara.
Oh...
Clara, no! Step away!
He's activating!
Clara, step away now! Don't...
Danny, Danny, if you can hear me,
if you're still there,
what are the clouds going to do?
The rain will fall again.
All humanity will die.
And rise again as Cybermen?
Correct.
How do we stop it?
We cannot be stopped.
Oh, that was BRILLIANT!
I love the telly here,
but did you see THAT?
Oh, Clara,
you poor thing,
you must feel like death.
Let me pop away the pain.
Don't you dare!
Don't you think about it!
Oh, sorry, hon, I'm just getting
a bit carried away.
It's your friends,
they're so more-ish.
Hmm?
Oh, stop looking all cross-pants.
I'm here to give you a gift.
Could you at least try
and be excited?
What gift?
Cyberdears!
Look at Mummy!!
Raise your arms.
Lower your arms.
Raise your right.
Lower your right. Turn on the spot.
There are exits at the front
and rear of the aircraft.
Please follow the lights up
the aisle. You see, Doctor?
The power to slaughter
whole worlds at a time,
then make them do a safety briefing.
Everyone who ever lived - man, woman
and child - is now at my command.
An indestructible army
to rage across the universe.
The more they kill,
the more they recruit.
Happy birthday.
Oh! You didn't know, did you?
It's lucky one of us
remembers these things.
Happy birthday...
♪ Mr President. ♪
Doctor.
Tiny bit pleased?
Oh, go on, crack a smile.
I want to see
if your eyebrows drop off.
All of this...
All of it, just to give me an army?
Well, I don't need one, do I?
Armies are for people
who think they're right.
And nobody thinks they're
righter than you!
Give a good man firepower,
and he'll never run
out of people to kill.
~ I don't want an army. ~ Well,
that's the trouble! Yes, you do!
You've always wanted one!
All those people
suffering in the Dalek camps?
Now you can save them.
All those bad guys
winning all the wars?
Go and get the good guys back.
~ Nobody can have that power. ~ You will
because you don't have a choice.
There's only way you can stop
these clouds from opening up
and killing all your little pets
down here.
Conquer the universe, Mr President.
Show a bad girl how it's done.
Why are you doing this?
I need you to know
we're not so different.
I need my friend back.
Every battle,
every war, every invasion -
from now on,
you decide the outcome.
What's the matter, Mr President?
Don't you trust yourself?
'Tell me.'
Am I a good man?
Sir!
I see into your soul, Doctor.
I see...
hatred.
I'm not a hero.
You are a good Dalek.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
I really didn't know. I wasn't sure.
You lose sight sometimes. Thank you!
I am NOT a good man!
And I'm not a bad man.
I am not a hero.
And I'm definitely not a president.
And, no, I'm not an officer.
Do you know what I am?
I...
am...
an idiot,
with a box
and a screwdriver.
Passing through,
helping out,
learning.
I don't need an army, I never have,
because I've got them.
Always them.
Because love,
it's not an emotion....
.. love is a promise.
And HE will NEVER hurt her.
PE, catch!
You didn't notice, did you?
While you where doing
all your silly orders,
while you where showing off,
the one soldier not obeying.
No, that's wrong, that's impossible.
The rain will not fall.
Oh? Why won't it?
The clouds will burn.
~ And who'll burn them?
~ I will burn them.
How?
I will burn.
One burning Cyberman is
hardly going to save the planet.
Correct.
Attention!
This is not a good day.
This is Earth's darkest hour.
And look at you miserable lot!
We are the fallen.
But today, we shall rise.
The army of the dead
will save the land of the living.
This is not
the order of a general...
.. nor the whim of a lunatic.
Excuse me?!
This is a promise!
The promise of a soldier!
You will sleep safe tonight.
Well.
The clouds have all gone.
Yes,
burned up,
totally burnt,
burnt to nothing.
Sorry.
10-0-11-00 by 02.
What did you say??
The current co-ordinates
of Gallifrey.
It's returned to
it's original location.
~ Didn't you ever think to look?
~ You are lying!
We can... We can go together.
Just you and me,
just like the old days.
You'd be clapped in irons.
If you like.
Doctor, I'm assuming
you'll remember those co-ordinates?
No. No, don't you dare,
I won't let you.
Old friend, is she?
If you have ever let
this creature live,
everything that happened today,
is on you.
All of it, on YOU.
And you're not going to
let her live again.
Clara... all I'm doing is not
letting you kill her.
I never said I was letting her live.
Really?
If that's the only thing
that will stop you...
.. yes.
Seriously(?)
(Oh...)
(Doctor.)
To save her soul?
But who, my dear, will save yours?
Say something nice.
Please?
You win.
I know.
Doctor!
Kate!
She's breathing.
She's alive! She can't be here!
She is.
She fell out of a plane!
The Cyberman...
.. must have caught her.
Doctor,
she's talking about her dad!
Of course!
The Earth's darkest hour
and mine.
Where else would you be?
(Thank you.)
'Clara...
'Clara...'
Danny?
Danny? Is that you?
Please say it's you.
~ 'Clara...' ~ The Doctor told me
about the bracelet,
how it can let Missy travel
from one world to the other.
'This place is dying now.'
Yes, but the bracelet
can bring you home.
'There's only enough power
for one trip.'
Then, come on. Hurry up!
'Just one trip.
'One trip, one person.'
Danny!
'You need to find his parents.
'He died a long time ago.'
'I'm sorry, Clara.
'I truly am.
'I had... I had promises to keep.'
~ Hey. ~ Hey. ~ I got your message.
~ Two weeks late. ~ Not bad. ~ Improving.
~ I see you've got news for me. ~ News?
He figured it out then?
PE figured out there was a way home.
Yeah. Yeah, he did.
Oh, good old PE.
He'll make a maths teacher yet.
Listen, Doctor. There's something
that I have to tell you and, um...
~ .. it's not good news
so just listen, OK? ~ I know.
~ Sorry? ~ I know exactly
what you've got to tell me.
~ You do?
~ You and Danny are together now.
That's great,
that's how it should be.
But the old man and the blue box,
that's never going to fit in.
So, no more flying around,
no more lying.
~ OK, no, that's not exactly...
~ It's fine.
No, it's NOT fine.
It... It really isn't... fine.
I've found Gallifrey!
Wow!
Oh, my God...
'I entered the co-ordinates,
'just like she said.'
And I found Gallifrey.
For once, she wasn't lying.
So, what are you going to do now?
Go home.
OK.
Gallifrey can be a good place.
I can help make it that.
~ What, you? ~ Shut up!
You won't just steal a TARDIS
and run away?
No, not this time. Never again.
Never again.
It's a long commute, so, you know
I thought, with you and Danny...
Yeah. Me and Danny.
Me and Danny,
we are going to be fine.
Don't you worry. You go home.
Go home.
Go be a king or something.
Yeah, I might do that.
Or queen, you know, whatever.
Yeah, queen,
that would be good, too.
Yeah...
Tell you what, seeing as it's
goodbye, shall we break a habit?
What? What habit?
Hug?
Why not.
Within reason.
Come on, you're on the clock.
Fair enough.
Why don't you like hugging, Doctor?
Never trust a hug...
.. it's just a way
to hide your face.
Yeah.
Doctor?
Travelling with you
made me feel really special.
Thank you for that.
Thank you for making me
feel special.
Thank you for exactly the same.
Coo-ee!
Hello?
Doctor! You know it can't end
like that!
Mm? We need to get this sorted
and quickly.
She's not all right, you know.
And neither are you.
I'm coming in.
Ah, there you are.
I knew I'd get round to you
eventually.
Now, stop gawping, and tell me...
what do you want for Christmas?
www.tvsubtitles.net